弓|<ゆ#|みがしなり弾|<は#|じけた焔|<ほ#|の#|お 夜|<よ空|ぞ#|らを凍|<こ#|おらせて
The bowstring strains, bursting flame that freezes the night sky
长弓震颤 迸裂的焰火 将夜空凝结
yu mi ga shi na ri ha ji ke ta ho no o yo zo ra o ko o ra se te
凜|<り#|んと蒼|<あ#|おく別|<わ#|か離|れの詩|<う#|たを 恋人|<あ#|な#|たを射|<うち堕|<おとす…
A cold blue elegy of parting, shooting down the lover...
凛然苍蓝的诀别之诗 将身为恋人的你射杀……
rin to a o ku wa ka re no u ta o a na ta o u chi o to su
遠|<と#|おい日|<ひの忘|<わ#|すれ物|<も#|の 引|<ひき裂|<さかれた傷|<き#|ず痕|あ#|と
A thing forgotten from distant days, the scars left torn asunder
遥远之日的遗留之物 被撕裂的道道伤痕
to o i hi no wa su re mo no hi ki sa ka re ta ki zu a to
呪|<の#|ろわれし約|<や#|#|く束|そ#|くをその胸|<む#|ねに宿|<や#|どして
The accursed vow harbored deep within that heart
将受诅咒的约定 刻入那胸膛之中
no ro wa re shi ya ku so ku o so no mu ne ni ya do shi te
「避|<さけられぬ終|<しゅ#|う焉|え#|んは せめて愛|<い#|としいその手|<てで…」
"The inescapable ending — at least let it come by your beloved hand..."
「无法逃避的结局 至少由那心爱之人亲手……」
sa ke ra re nu shu u en wa se me te i to shi i so no te de
抗|<あ#|ら#|がえぬ衝|<しょ#|う動|ど#|うの闇|<や#|みが彼|<か#|れを包|<つ#|#|つんだ…
The darkness of irresistible impulse enveloped him...
无法抗拒的疯狂冲动 将他笼罩吞噬……
a ra ga e nu sho u do u no ya mi ga ka re o tsu tsun da
歪|<ゆ#|がむ世|<せ|界|か#|い螺|<ら旋|せ#|んの焔|<ほ#|の#|お 輪|<り#|ん回|ねを貫|<つ#|ら#|ぬいて
A warped world, spiral flames piercing through the cycle of rebirth
扭曲世界的螺旋之焰 贯穿轮回往复
yu ga mu se ka i ra sen no ho no o rin ne o tsu ra nu i te
凜|<り#|んと緋|<あ#|かく血|<ち途|ぬれくちづけ 恋人|<あ#|な#|たを射|<うち堕|<おとす…
A cold crimson kiss stained with blood, shooting down the lover...
凛然绯红的血濡之吻 将身为恋人的你射杀……
rin to a ka ku chi nu re ku chi zu ke a na ta o u chi o to su
忘|<わ#|すレモノハ在|<あリマセンカ
Is there nothing you have left behind...?
还有什么忘记了吗？……
wa su re mo no wa a ri ma sen ka
古|<い#|に#|し#|えの伝|<でん説|せ#|つ その魔|<ま物|も#|のに傷|<き#|ずを負|<おわされた者|<も#|のは
In an ancient legend: one who is wounded by that demon
古老的传说中 被那魔物所伤之人
i ni shi e no den se tsu so no ma mo no ni ki zu o o wa sa re ta mo no wa
呪|<の#|ろいが全|<ぜん身|しんを駈|<かけ回|<め#|ぐり
The curse courses through their entire body
诅咒将于全身游走奔涌
no ro i ga zen shin o ka ke me gu ri
やがては同|<お#|なじ魔|<ま物|も#|のに成|<なり果|<はてるだろう…
And before long shall become the very same demon...
终有一日 会化作同样的魔物吧…
ya ga te wa o na ji ma mo no ni na ri ha te ru da ro u
その傷|<き#|ずを負|<おったのはいつ？
When was that wound inflicted?
那伤痕又是什么时候留下的？
so no ki zu o o tta no wa i tsu
それは二|<ふ#|た人|りが出|<で会|あったあの日|<ひまで溯|<さ#|か#|の#|ぼる
It traces back to the day the two first met
那要追溯至二人相遇的那一天
so re wa fu ta ri ga de a tta a no hi ma de sa ka no bo ru
彼|<か#|れが彼|<か#|の女|じょを助|<た#|すけた時|<と#|きに負|<おった傷|<き#|ず
The wound he sustained when he saved her
那是他为救她时所受的伤
ka re ga ka no jo o ta su ke ta to ki ni o tta ki zu
全|<す#|べては出|<で会|あった時|<と#|きから始|<は#|じまっていた…
Everything had begun from the moment they met...
一切自相遇之时 便已悄然开始……
su be te wa de a tta to ki ka ra ha ji ma tte i ta
岀|<で会|あいは喪|<そう失|し#|つへの約|<や#|く束|そ#|く…
Their meeting was a promise of loss...
相遇即是通往相离的约定……
te a i wa so u shi tsu e no ya ku so ku
枯|<かれ果|<はてた涙|<な#|み#|だは 哀|<か#|なしみの蒼|<あ#|おい焔|<ほ#|の#|おを宿|<や#|どし
Tears long withered harbor a sorrowful blue flame
干涸殆尽的泪水 宿有悲伤的苍蓝之焰
ka re ha te ta na mi da wa ka na shi mi no a o i ho no o o ya do shi
銀|<ぎん色|い#|ろに輝|<か#|が#|やく矢|<やを放|<は#|なつ
Loosing an arrow that gleams with silver light
射出闪耀银色光辉的箭矢
gin i ro ni ka ga ya ku ya o ha na tsu
何|<なん度|<どでも 唯|<た#|だ…彼|<か#|れが息|<い#|き絶|<たえるまで…
Again and again, only... until he draws his final breath...
无论多少次 直至……他气绝而亡……
nan do de mo ta da ka re ga i ki ta e ru ma de
どうして…
Why...
怎么会……
do u shi te
愛|<あ#|いする人|<ひ#|とを失|<う#|し#|なった世|<せ界|か#|いには
In a world that has lost its beloved one
在失去所爱之人的世界里
a i su ru hi to o u shi na tta se ka i ni wa
どんな色|<い#|ろの花|<は#|なが咲|<さくだろう？
What color flowers shall ever bloom?
会绽放何种色彩的花呢？
don na i ro no ha na ga sa ku da ro u
月|<つ#|きを抱|<だいた十|<じゅ#|う字|じの焔|<ほ#|の#|お 茨|<い#|ば#|らを倦|<まきつけて
A cruciform flame embracing the moon, wound endlessly with briars
环抱月华的十字之焰 荆棘缠绕不倦
tsu ki o da i ta ju u ji no ho no o i ba ra o ma ki tsu ke te
凜|<り#|んと白|<し#|ろく最|<さ#|い期|ごの弓矢|<ア#|ロ#|ー 私|<わ#|た#|しを射|<うち堕|<おとす…
A cold white arrow of the final hour, shooting me down...
凛然纯白的临终箭矢 将身为恋人的我射杀……
rin to shi ro ku sa i go no a ro o wa ta shi o u chi o to su
愛|<あいする人|<ほ#|とを失|<う#|し#|なった世|<せ界|か#|いにはどんな色|<い#|ろの花|<は#|なが咲|<さく…
In a world that has lost its beloved one, what color flowers shall bloom...
在失去所爱之人的世界里 会绽放何种色彩的花……
a i su ru hi to o u shi na tta se ka i ni wa don na i ro no ha na ga sa ku
愛|<あいする人|<ほ#|とを失|<う#|し#|なった世|<せ界|か#|いにはどんな色|<い#|ろの花|<は#|なが咲|<さく…
In a world that has lost its beloved one, what color flowers shall bloom...
在失去所爱之人的世界里 会绽放何种色彩的花……
a i su ru hi to o u shi na tta se ka i ni wa don na i ro no ha na ga sa ku
愛|<あいする人|<ほ#|とを失|<う#|し#|なった世|<せ界|か#|いにはどんな色|<い#|ろの花|<は#|なが咲|<さく…
In a world that has lost its beloved one, what color flowers shall bloom...
在失去所爱之人的世界里 会绽放何种色彩的花……
a i su ru hi to o u shi na tta se ka i ni wa don na i ro no ha na ga sa ku
愛|<あいする人|<ほ#|とを失|<う#|し#|なった世|<せ界|か#|いにはどんな色|<い#|ろの花|<は#|なが咲|<さく…
In a world that has lost its beloved one, what color flowers shall bloom...
在失去所爱之人的世界里 会绽放何种色彩的花……
a i su ru hi to o u shi na tta se ka i ni wa don na i ro no ha na ga sa ku
愛|<あいする人|<ひ#|とを失|<う#|し#|なった世|<せ界|か#|いにはどんな色|<い#|ろの花|<は#|なが咲|<さく…
In a world that has lost its beloved one, what color flowers shall bloom...
在失去所爱之人的世界里 会绽放何种色彩的花……
a i su ru hi to o u shi na tta se ka i ni wa don na i ro no ha na ga sa ku
愛|<あいする人|<ほ#|とを失|<う#|し#|なった世|<せ界|か#|いにはどんな色|<い#|ろの花|<は#|なが咲|<さく…
In a world that has lost its beloved one, what color flowers shall bloom...
在失去所爱之人的世界里 会绽放何种色彩的花……
a i su ru hi to o u shi na tta se ka i ni wa don na i ro no ha na ga sa ku
愛|<あいする人|<ほ#|とを失|<う#|し#|なった世|<せ界|か#|いにはどんな色|<い#|ろの花|<は#|なが咲|<さく…
In a world that has lost its beloved one, what color flowers shall bloom...
在失去所爱之人的世界里 会绽放何种色彩的花……
a i su ru hi to o u shi na tta se ka i ni wa don na i ro no ha na ga sa ku
愛|<あいする人|<ほ#|とを失|<う#|し#|なった世|<せ界|か#|いにはどんな色|<い#|ろの花|<は#|なが咲|<さく…
In a world that has lost its beloved one, what color flowers shall bloom...
在失去所爱之人的世界里 会绽放何种色彩的花……
a i su ru hi to o u shi na tta se ka i ni wa don na i ro no ha na ga sa ku